{
	"item": [{
		"question": "What is the meaning of HTML?",
		"answer": "Hypertext Mark-up Language"
	}, {
		"question": "It is intended for providing accessibility.",
		"answer": "WAI-ARAI"
	}, {
		"question": "An easily parsed structure that allows users to create their own tags.",
		"answer": "XML"
	}, {
		"question": "It is commonly used as an escape sequence.",
		"answer": "Character References"
	}, {
		"question": "It forbids the use of deprecated elements.",
		"answer": "Strict"
	}, {
		"question": "HTML attribute that specifies the destination of the link",
		"answer": "href"
	}, {
		"question": "An element used to indicate an ordered list",
		"answer": "ol"
	}, {
		"question": "It is used to identify the language of the document",
		"answer": "lang"
	}, {
		"question": "It is strictly formatted as XML.",
		"answer": "XHTML"
	}, {
		"question": "It allows deprecated elements for backward compatibility.",
		"answer": "Transitional"
	}]
}